《反恐特警队》前情提要
Previously on SWAT...
我们现在瞄准了韩国城中
We're targeting a huge fentanyl operation
大量制造芬太尼的犯罪活动
being run out of Koreatown.
如果你想要你儿子活命
If you want your son back alive,
你必须一个人来见我们
you'll meet us alone.
我就知道你会来
I knew you'd come.
绑架沃尔什儿子的真正幕后主使
The real top dog who kidnapped Walsh's son
杰·金 都没有被抓到
isn't even in custody-- Jae Kim.
警官  显然这里面产生了误会
Officer, there's obviously some sort of misunderstanding.
你追杀的那对母子
对我来说就像家人一般
You went after a mother and son who are like family to me.
他上周想回全日制学校上课
He tried to do a full day back at school last week.
其实还没准备好
Wasn't ready.
被绑架 性命受到威胁
Well, getting kidnapped, your life threatened,
刀架脖子上 肯定会让人乱了方寸
a knife held to your neck will mess you up a little bit.
要恢复原样是需要时间的
It's just gonna take him a little time to bounce back.
他做得很棒 是我没准备好
He's doing fine; I'm the one that wasn't ready.
自那以后 就不敢让他离开视线
Haven't been able to let him out of my sight since then.
这样不健康
It's not healthy.
我得让他重新做回一个孩子
I got to let him start being a kid again,
但杰·金彻底改变了我们的生活
but Jae Kim turned our lives inside out.
听我说
Okay, listen to me.
我们很快就能抓到他了
We are very close to taking him down.
只差最后一步
We just need that final piece.
我们现在还没证据 也许永远都拿不到
We don't have one by now, maybe we never will.
我们很接近了  KC
We are close, K.C.
金拒绝谈及制造芬太尼的行动
Kim buttoned up his fentanyl operation, but he's gonna have
但他早晚要露出马脚
to dip back in sooner or later.
一旦他暴露  我们一定到场
And when he does, we're gonna be there.
和他见面的新面孔是谁
And who's the new guy he's meeting with?
我们还没查到名字
We don't have a name yet,
但他的车子登记在县里
but his car is registered to the county.
他看着不会有很多线索
He doesn't look like a big shot.
也许不是关于他 他只是个媒介
Maybe it's not about him, but what he can access.
不管怎么样 我都会查清楚
Either way, I aim to find out.
你说有三把
You said there were three.
不好意思 应该是四把
My fault, I guess there are four.
你得学着记住这些
You need to learn to keep track.
厨房刀必须放在一起
Kitchen knives need to stay together.
我想我应该把藏在
I guess I'd better get rid of the shank
浴室里的杆子丢掉
I stashed in the bathroom.
你自己也看到了
Hey, listen. You saw for yourself.
我的武器都安全存放 枪也很安全
My weapons are all secure. We got the gun safe.
我们完全按规章行事
We're following all the regulations.
真的要把所有刀具都查一遍吗
We really need to go over cutlery?
我得去工作了
I just... I got to get to work.
到工作的地方让你的上司签个名
Oh, have your supervisor sign this while you're there.
我以为口头说说就行
I thought I could just loop 'em in verbally.
跳过这些形式主义
Skip the formality.
有关假释的任何事都不是形式主义
Uh, nothing about parole's a formality.
洛城警局需要知道是否有警官
LAPD needs to know if there's an officer
和被判刑的重罪犯一起住
residing with a convicted felon.
知道了  没问题  长官
Got it. It's not a problem, ma'am.
没拿到签名之前就是有问题
It is until I get that signature.
法官要我说得非常明白
The judge wanted me to be perfectly clear.
别以为自己是警察就有优待
Don't expect favors because you're a cop.
抱歉  难道你是在帮我
I'm sorry. Were you doing me
而我却没有意识到吗
some kind of favor that I missed?
如果你母亲在假释期间违反...
If your mother violates parole while living...
很明白
It's clear.
非常明白  长官
Perfectly, ma'am.
不能喝酒
No alcohol.
当然还有走私品也不可以
Same thing goes for contraband, obviously.
如果你计划离开洛杉矶县
And if you're planning on leaving Los Angeles County,
最起码要通知我
I need you to notify me at least...
我知道  十八年牢狱生活后
Well, I know, after 18 years,
在这个县里就可以有很多可以做的事情
I'm sure there's plenty to do here in this county.
如有出行变化 最起码提前三天
That changes, notify me through the app
通过应用软件通知我
three days prior to travel.
下周见  凯伦
See you next week, Karen.
好了
Okay.
很抱歉冰箱那么空
I'm sorry the fridge is so bare.
我给你留了点现金 就在手机旁边
I did leave you some cash by your phone
以防你出去找工作需要
if you want to get a bite while you're out job hunting.
手机 我不知道手机在哪里
My pho... I don't know where my phone is.
老妈 手机在你床上充电呢
Ma, it's-it's charging by your bed.
不 吉米 是你的床
No, Jimmy, it's your bed. Okay?
我还是没习惯
I still don't feel right about this.
我要睡在沙发上
I-I'm gonna sleep on the couch.
我知道 我知道自己是一个累赘
I mean, I-I know that I'm a burden to you.
我知道的
I can feel it.
妈  听着
Ma, Ma. Listen.
对我们俩来说这是一个全新的开始
This is a fresh start for both of us.
祝你今天过得愉快
Have a great day, okay?
-好  -好吗
- Hmm. ‭- Okay?
好的
Okay.
来用吧  老兄
Here you go, man.
-用吧  -谢了
- Go ahead. - ‭Thanks.
健康部门的
Health Department?
财产评估的
Property Assessment.
你是
You're, um...
抱歉 脑子一片空白 提醒我一下
Forgive me, I'm blanking. Uh, remind me.
伊恩·派克
Ian Peck.
我们之前见过
We meet before?
不 但我们有个共同的朋友
No, no. We have a mutual friend.
杰·金
‭Jae Kim.
你也是干房地产的吗
You're, uh... in real estate, too?
我和金有个没结束的项目
I have an unfinished project with Kim.
听着比我的工作更合算
Sounds much more lucrative than my line of work.
公关事务
Public sector.
我也是
Me, too.
洛城警局
LAPD.
你要不要谈谈你跟金在搞什么
You want to tell me what you got cooking with Kim?
他有财产 我帮他评估 于是有了交集
He owns property. I assess its value, so we've crossed paths.
你和开发商周日经常会在
How often do you meet with developers on Sundays
荒废的建筑工地见面吗
in deserted construction sites?
因为我看着觉得很可疑
'Cause that seems pretty damn suspicious to me.
这只是简单地见个面
It was just a simple meeting.
那我要是查你的银行流水
So if I was to dig into your bank statements,
不会找到金给你转账的记录咯
I wouldn't see any wire transfers from Kim to you?
不会找到你账上有非正常收入
Any unexplained cash hitting your account?
誓死忠诚
Loyal till the end, huh?
行了 我懂 金是你的金主
All right, I get it, Kim's the money.
我不过就是个在男厕所偶遇的人
I'm a guy you just met in a men's bathroom.
我说  他在干嘛
I mean, what's he doing?
把你安排在一群
Setting you up with his stable
一小时收费一千刀的律师中间
of a-thousand-dollar-an-hour lawyers?
肯定是这样
I mean, he's got to be.
不然你怎么会出现在这里
I mean, why else would you be headed down this road?
-我没有律师  -你没有吗
- I don't have any lawyers. - You don't?
你真觉得公设辩护律师
Do you really think that some public defender's
会尽力为你免除长期徒刑吗
gonna keep you from doing hard time?
长期徒刑
Hard time?
要是有人坐牢 那必须是...
If anyone should be doing hard time, it's...
听着
Listen.
金不只是什么...
Kim is not just some...
不 不 没办法把他和任何事联系起来
No, no. It is impossible to tie him to anything.
他的关系网太深了
He's too connected.
对我来说不是
Not for me, he's not.
只要对他有用 金下一次就会把你整惨
Kim's gonna screw you the next time he needs to,
如果他没有 我也会的
and if he doesn't, I will.
所以干嘛不先发制人
So why not screw him first?
他的名字被刷在大楼上
His name's plastered on buildings.
他们给他颁奖 请他去剪彩
He wins awards. He-he cuts ribbons.
但没人知道他到底有多坏
But no one knows how bad he really is.
我知道  相信我  我知道
Oh, I do. Trust me, I do.
我就是需要证据
I just need proof.
派克给了什么
So what's Peck handing over?
伪造的地契  许可证  应有尽有  KC
Forged deeds, permits, you name it, K.C.
皮卡大道项目显然
That Pico-Corridor project
只是金最近的骗局
was just Kim's latest scam, apparently.
派克伪造文件  高估他的财产
Peck forged documents to overvalue his property?
难道不应该是反着来吗
Shouldn't it be the other way around?
我猜  金把皮卡大道作为抵押物时
Well, my guess is, when Kim put Pico-Corridor up as collateral,
他必须确保这足够
he needed to make sure it was enough
贷款2500万
to secure a $25 million loan.
芬太尼制毒点被我们清扫之后
He was hard up for cash
他资金短缺  但是贷款
after we made that fentanyl bust, but that loan,
明天就到账
it comes due tomorrow.
那么我们给金定什么罪
So, what do we nail Kim on?
房地产诈骗
Real estate fraud?
他应该有更大的罪名
He deserves to go away for far worse,
但自从被我们清扫之后 他一直靠着
but he's been sitting on the rest of his fentanyl supply
剩下的货赚钱
since that bust.
所以这也许是我们的最好机会 把这混蛋
So this might be our best chance to put that son of a bitch away
关上至少十几年
你什么时候准备公开调查
for a decade or more. When do you want to go public with this?
洛城警局可能没那么高兴
LAPD might not be so thrilled
他们没找到的东西 我们却找到了
we found something they couldn't.
未记录在案不代表非法
Off the books doesn't mean illegal.
有确切的证据在手才是关键 KC
A smoking gun is still a smoking gun, K.C.,
相信我
and trust me,
他们会很高兴进行搜捕
they'll be happy to have the bust.
即使是被退休缉毒局探员
Even if it's uncovered by a retired DEA agent
-和不当班的警察发现的 -即使这样
- and an off-duty cop? - Even then.
派克说一小时后和他在餐馆见面
Peck says to meet him at the diner in an hour.
洪都 你还好吗
Hondo, are you all right?
洪都
Hondo!
反恐特警队
第一季  第二十集
-幸好你没事 -你被截杀了
- Thank God you're all right. - You got cut up.
-我还没死 -好样的
- I'm still standing. - ‭Attaboy.‬
-我是洪都
-约翰·巴罗斯 劫案凶杀专案组
- I'm Hondo. ‭- John Burrows, RHD.‬
你能告诉我一下发生了些什么吗
You want to run me through what went down?
一辆车在红灯那里停下来
A car pulled up over there by the stoplight.
他们开火前 我就感觉到
I could tell something was off with these three
他们三个不太对 我就踩油门倒车
before they opened fire, so I punched the gas
我们在那里撞上了
and we ended up over there.
我从车里出来 向第一名枪手开了两枪
I got out and I dropped the first shooter with two rounds.
司机肩膀中了枪 但没能阻止他跑
The driver took a bullet to the shoulder, but he kept his feet
他和第二名枪手向东边逃了
and he fled east with the second shooter.
这些是弹壳
Here's the shell casings.
-金伯公司（反恐特警队配枪制造商）
可以验证 -对方是路怒症吗
- Kimber's on its way to evidence. - Some kind of road rage thing?
不 这是场有计划的袭击
我知道是谁指使的
No, this was a planned hit and I know who was behind it.
杰·金
Jae Kim.
-那个地产巨头  -没错
- The mogul developer guy? - That's right.
我空闲时间都在查金
I've been digging into Kim on my free time.
-我们一直在监控他的行动
-你们是谁
- We've been doing surveillance on him. - ‭Who's we?‬
我和KC·沃尔什
Me and K.C. Walsh.
-退休缉毒局探员沃尔什吗
-我三个月前就告诉你
- Retired DEA Agent Walsh? - I told you three months ago
-让毒品调查科管这事 -我这么做了
- to leave the investigating to Narcotics. - ‭And I did.‬
但当我再去核实进展的时候
发现他们根本就没管这件事
But when I checked back in, they hadn't moved the ball an inch.
你做了什么吗 长官
What about you, sir?
你有关注过这件事的进度吗
Did you follow up with them in any of this?
不 你没有
No, you didn't.
我把金让给你和毒品调查科去查
I handed you and Narcotics Kim on a silver platter
却没有人管 所以我决定自己去做
and nobody did nothing, so I decided to.
如果我们出警看到了一个警官的尸体
And how would your little hobby look if we were responding
你这业余活动在别人眼里会是什么样
to an officer killed call here?
我没有让这种事发生
I didn't let that happen.
好吧
Okay.
整理干净 回总部
Get cleaned up and head back to HQ.
总部 你不能现在就把我撤回去 长官
HQ? No. You're not pulling me off this right now, sir.
你既是受害人 也是唯一的目击证人
You're both our victim and our only witness,
所以你不能继续参与办案了
so you're not staying in the field.
-洪都 你知道规定的  -取消它
- Hondo, you know the protocol. - ‭Waive it.‬
然后你可以继续这么干吗 不行
So you can keep playing cowboy? Denied.
把你知道的信息都告诉巴罗斯
在总部协助办案
Get whatever intel you have to Burrows and assist from HQ.
你没事就好 头儿
Glad you're okay, boss.
-谁干的  -你还记得那个
- Yo, who did this? - Do you remember the guy
绑架KC·沃尔什儿子的背后指使者吗
behind the kidnapping of K.C. Walsh's son?
什么 杰·金 那个有钱的开发商吗
What, Jae Kim? The-the rich developer dude?
芬太尼制毒链倒了 金没事
Fentanyl ring went down, Kim never did.
你怎么知道是他干的
How do you know he did this?
我一直在查他的生意
I kept digging into his businesses
显然我触到他的神经了 他派人来追杀我
and clearly I hit a nerve. He sent his goons after me.
我需要你们的帮助
Look, I need your help.
你们来的路上
有听到什么有帮助的线索吗
Did you hear anything on the way over here that we can use?
枪和车的编号都磨掉了
Gun and vehicle are scrubbed.
身亡的枪手无法确认身份
No ID on the dead shooter.
-他有纹身吗 -肩胛骨处有个狼头
- He got any ink? - Wolf head on his shoulder blade.
先知帮 绝对是他们
Profetas. Yeah, definitely the Profetas.
他们还在博伊尔高地吗
Are they still in Boyle Heights?
他们被卷入了一场地盘争夺战
搬去南盖特了
They got caught up in a turf war, moved to South Gate.
不管他们在哪 司机肩部中枪了
Well, wherever they are, the driver's got a bullet
所以他跑不了多远
in his shoulder, so he ain't getting too far.
好了  听着
All right, look.
希克斯想让我回总部
Hicks wants me anchored at HQ.
斯特里特 我房间里有个盒子
Street, there's a box in my den at my house.
你和克里斯一起去
你们把那个给巴罗斯
You take Chris with you, you get it to Burrows.
-他是劫案凶杀专案组的人 -好的
- He's running point for RHD. - All right.
这些先知帮的人 你想让我们怎么抓他们
These Profetas, how do you want us to go after 'em?
敌人的敌人永远不是一个坏的开始
The enemy of your enemy is never a bad place to start.
知道我在说什么吗
Know what I'm saying?
-这不算告密  -不
- So it's not considered snitching. - No?
-罗斯科  -我认识你吗
- Hey, Roscoe. - ‭I know you?‬
去年抓了你的兄弟
Busted your brother last year.
-这和我有什么关系 -新姑娘吗
- What's that got to do with me? - New girl?
还有待考察
Was about to find out.
我没做什么值得你们大张旗鼓前来的事
I didn't do anything to deserve this parade,
你们来找我干啥 大哥
so why y'all bothering me, dawg?
你知道往那边1.5公里
You know anything about an attempted hit on a cop
有人试图袭击警察吗
about a mile that way?
不 我在这儿一整天了 大哥
Nope. Nope. I've been here all day, dawg.
你可以问任何人
You can ask anybody.
我们有理由认为先知帮参与其中
Well, we got reason to think Los Profetas were involved.
那在你们看来我现在像一个
Now, do I look like a freaking
-先知帮的成员吗 -更像是一九帮的
- Los Profetas to you? - More like a One-Niner.
先知帮一直在抢夺你们的地盘 不是吗
Profetas have been moving in on you and your crew, haven't they?
-是有一些侵占问题
-如果他们正好被突袭了
- There's been some encroachment, yeah. ‭- So it wouldn't be
对你们来说也不算坏事吧
the worst thing if they happened to get raided.
-突袭  -我们突袭
- Raided? ‭- By us.
今天 你告诉我们他们
Today. You tell us where they might
可能会在哪里出现 你给我们一些
be posted up, you give us some good intel
对审判有用的情报
on what we might find that's good enough for a judge...
我们会拿下他们
And we take 'em down.
等会儿 让我弄清楚
Now hold on, let me get this straight.
你们这么大老远过来就是为了
Y'all came all the way down here just to give me the chance
给我个机会让先知帮不好过
to make some Los Profetas miserable?
靠
Hell.
你们怎么不早说
Why didn't y'all just say so?
照片 日期
Photos, dates.
哈里森警司记录了一打过去两个月
Sergeant Harrelson documented a dozen afterhours meetings
金在非常规时间的会面
Kim had over the last two months.
记录得非常详细
It's so thorough.
洪都做事一直都很靠谱
Hondo doesn't do half-assed.
这里的证据足以起诉金吗
Is there enough here to charge Kim?
这些电汇的时间点
Well, the time codes on these wire transfers
与洪都记录的会面时间大致匹配
match up with most of Hondo's meeting log,
但是这还不够我们去起诉他
but there's nothing we could prosecute for, yet.
而且伊恩·派克也没在餐厅出现
And there is no sign of this Ian Peck at that diner.
你觉得洪都是不是陷得太深了
Hey, uh, think Hondo might've got too deep here?
我觉得金还不知道他惹上谁了
I think Kim has no clue who he's messed with.
有什么不对劲吗
Something wrong?
十八年真的是一段很长的时间
18 years really is a long time.
这个地方就像是个未来世界
This place is really the future.
你能想象到的都有
All you need is, like, flying cars.
你来这干什么  你怎么进来的
What are you doing here? H-How did you get inside?
前面的那家伙话太多了
Oh, the guy at the front is a bit of a talker--
你猜怎么着
so, guess what.
我申请的其中一个工作单位回我电话了
One of the jobs that I applied for, they called,
他们想在今天见我
and they want to meet me, today.
♪ 你老妈我还是有市场的 ♪
♪ Your mama is still employable. ♪
那挺好的  但是你不能
That is great, but you can't
这样出现 骗别人放你进这里
just show up here and scam your way
我是说 我有可能
inside the building, I mean, I could get
会因此惹上麻烦的
in serious trouble for this.
我不认为"来看我儿子"是骗人的
I-I didn't think that visiting my son was a scam.
我就是想看看你工作的地方
I-I just wanted to see where you work.
我没有撒谎
I mean, I didn't lie or anything.
你才刚刚假释出来
You're just out on parole.
这对我来说不是很好 仅此而已
It's not really a good look for me right now, that's all.
好吧
Okay.
我带了这个给你 因为需要你签字
I brought you this, because you need to have it signed,
而且你知道
And you know, I mean,
我不想给你惹麻烦
I don't want to cause any trouble for you.
好的  谢谢
Okay, thank you.
所以
So...
-我该从这边走吗  -对的
- So should I leave that way? - Yeah.
那样最好
That'd be great.
我放了个音响在我车里
I put one of those stereos in my car, man.
音效非常棒的
It sounds great.
-洛城警局 马上趴下
-洛城警局 特警队
- LAPD! Get on the ground now! - LAPD! SWAT!
-不许动 不许动 -已经控制
- Don't move! Don't move! - A Code 4 here!
右侧安全
Right side clear!
两两一组
Give me a two! ‭Two!
看起来是偷来的音响设备
Looks like stolen stereo equipment.
右侧安全 这里有个受伤的疑犯
Right side clear! Got a wounded suspect in here.
我来叫救援小组的
I'll get an R/A rolling.
让我来看看你的小黄脸
Let me see those pearly yellows.
把那东西从我脸上拿开
Get that thing out of my face.
-另外那家伙在哪 -不知道你说谁
- Where's the other guy? - Don't know no other guy.
那个逃跑的枪手 加布里埃尔
The shooter that got away, Gabriel.
轮到你说话了
It's time for you to talk.
去死吧
Go to hell.
还记得今天早上要杀的那个警察吗
Know the cop that you guys tried to kill this morning?
坏消息是他没死
The bad news is he's not dead.
更坏的消息是
他认出你是那个逃跑的司机
Worse news is, he just ID'd you as the getaway driver.
一个枪手死了
如果你是唯一一个上法庭的人
One shooter's dead, and if you're the only guy on trial...
我没有对警察开枪
I didn't shoot at no cop.
司机和那些开枪的人
The driver is just as responsible
一样都有罪
as the guys slinging the bullets,
除非你知道那个逃跑的枪手在哪
so unless you know where the missing shooter is...
迪亚高·佩雷斯
Diego Perez.
大块头 山羊胡
Big guy, goatee.
我昨晚接的他
I picked him up last night.
他是从维加斯来干活的
He came in from Vegas to pull the job.
职业杀手吗
Contract killer?
金想置身事外
Kim's trying to keep clean.
金 她是谁
Kim? Who's she?
他想杀了你
So he tries to kill you,
但我们还没有足够证据逮捕他
but we still don't have enough to make an arrest?
我们会找到证据的 KC 听着
We will, K.C. Listen.
金借走了2500万贷款
That $25 million dollar loan Kim took out,
我们可以从那里着手
there's something I can put into motion.
贷款
Loan?
我们得找到派克
We need to find Peck.
他有皮卡大道项目的文件
He's the one with the Pico Corridor papers.
那个东西能让金坐牢 保护卡尔文
That's what's gonna put Kim away and keep Calvin safe.
听着 别泄气 好吗 我让我的队员
Look, just hang tight, all right? I got the rest of my team
跟进这个案子 交给我们
working on this, let us do our thing.
已经发布了迪亚高·佩雷斯的全境通告
APB's out on Diego Perez,
还没消息
haven't gotten a hit yet.
他可能用了化名 或许我们可以让洛克
He's probably got an alias. Maybe we can get Rocker
等那个司机手术做完后给他施点压
to put some pressure on our driver once he's out of surgery.
我已经让你禁足了 你要去哪
I grounded you. Where you going?
打击帮派调查组
要我去法务部签一份声明
CAPO unit needs me to sign a statement over in Legal.
对  对  对  好吧
Ah, right, right, right, okay.
替我向马蒂问好
Well, give Marty my best.
弄完就回来
Then get back here.
来了
Hey, there he is.
感谢前来
Thanks for coming.
请坐
Have a seat.
关于那份文书...
About that paperwork...
打扰一下  女士
Excuse me, ma'am.
你是卡洛琳·肖恩吗
You Carolyn Shaw?
企业贷款的副总裁
VP of Corporate Loans?
您有什么事  警官
What's this about, Officer?
其实我是"警司"
It's, uh, "sergeant," Actually.
我想咨询下你们一位客户的情况 杰·金
I just have a question about your clients, Jae Kim.
如果你的银行准备给他贷款2500万
If your bank was to loan him 25 million,
需要你的签字 对吗
you'd be the one to sign off on it, right?
我不会讨论客户的信息
Well, I don't discuss individual clients...
听着 我本不应该告诉你的 但在你
Look, I shouldn't tell you this, but before you get
与杰·金有进一步合作前
more wrapped up in the Jae Kim business,
我觉得你应该知道他正在被调查
I think you should know he's under investigation.
调查什么
Investigation for what?
洗钱 走私毒品
Money laundering, drug trafficking,
企图谋杀警官 都是他的罪名
attempted murder of a police officer, take your pick.
我本不应该帮你
Now, I'm not supposed to do this favor for you.
我可能会为此惹上很多麻烦
I could really get in a lot of trouble warning you like this,
但我不想因为他的问题
让你的银行受到牵连
but I'd hate to see his problems drag your bank down with him.
难以置信 我刚准备
I can't believe it, I was just about to approve
对他的贷款批准展期
an extension on his loan payment.
我不是金融人士
但如果是我 我会三思的
Well, I'm no banker, but I'd think twice before you do that.
金会落网的
Kim's going down.
别说是我告诉你的
You didn't hear that from me.
谢谢你
Thank you.
祝你今天愉快
Have a nice day.
是我
Yeah, it's me.
你跟我说了...
You told me...
他看上去非常生气
He looks really pissed.
是啊 我猜他刚发现
Yeah, I'm guessing he's just found out he's gonna
他必须得在明早前还清贷款了
have to pay back that loan by tomorrow morning.
洪都下一步要怎么做
So what Hondo's next move?
请放下后车窗
Roll the back window down, please.
还记得我吗
You remember me?
有次我开会不请自来的警官
The officer who dropped in on one of my meetings a while back.
我当然记得
Sure, I remember.
我一直没记住你的名字
I never did get your name.
反恐特警队的丹尼尔·哈里森
It's Daniel Harrelson, SWAT.
我很想知道你今天过得怎样
Just wondering how your day is going so far.
你真的不该
You really shouldn't meddle
搅和到别人的私事中去
in another person's private business.
是啊
或许你几个月前就该听取我的建议了
Yeah, maybe you should've taken your own advice four months ago.
我只想告诉你
I just want you to know,
下次咱俩见面时
the next time we see each other,
你就会带上手铐
you will be wearing cuffs.
好好享受你余下的日子
I hope you enjoy the time you have left.
派克的车有停车通行证
Peck's county car has a parking pass,
这座大楼也隶属于金旗下一家公司
and building's owned by one of Kim's LLCs.
他就是金的人
The guy's on Kim's payroll.
看起来哈里森警司发现了什么
Seems like Sergeant Harrelson was onto something.
是他吗
That him?
伊恩·派克 好吧 事情不妙
Ian Peck. Okay, that's not good.
房间里还有人
Somebody's still here.
KC
K.C.?
不
No.
我来的时候他就已经死了
I-I found him like that.
靠墙
Against the wall.
我准备报警的
I was gonna call it in,
就是还没机会...
I just hadn't had a chance to do...
-快  -等下
- Now. ‭- Wait a second.
怎么
What...?
派克跟踪你了吗 你是因为自卫杀了他吗
Did Peck come after you? Did you kill him in self-defense?
我们发现现场只有你和受害者
你也没有报警
You were found alone with the victim, you didn't call it in.
你非法闯入
You were there illegally.
我们还发现你在搜那个房间
We found you searching the place.
你怎么解释
How do you explain that?
我知道了他的地址 就去那找那些
I got his address, I went there to get the papers
他说能给杰·金定罪的文件
然后我就发现他已经死了
he said would incriminate Jae Kim and I found him dead.
我是要报警的 但我想先看看
I was gonna call it in, but I wanted to see
文件还在不在
if the paperwork was still there first.
我不该这么做的 但是
I shouldn't have done it, but...
-她没有杀他  -我理解
- She didn't kill him. ‭- I understand
你为什么相信她 但从表面看无法判定
why you believe that, but that's not how it looks.
是金刻意让KC偶然发现派克的住址的
Kim made sure K.C. came across Peck's address.
我不知道是用什么办法
And I don't know how,
但他想通过陷害她来警告我
but he set her up to get to me.
如果是这样 你和你的
If that's true, traipsing around L.A.
兼职女神探朋友在洛杉矶闲逛
with your moonlighting gal pal put her in that chair,
导致她如此下场
and got us no closer to nailing Kim
也并没有帮助我们给金定罪
than we were in the first place.
你清楚罪犯会是什么样
You know what guilty looks like,
你也清楚她没有杀那个人
and you know she didn't kill that guy.
我是凶案组的 我见过那么多悬案
I'm homicide. On the scale of mysteries,
这个的证据算很充分了
this isn't much of one.
沃尔什和尸体在案发现场同时被发现
Walsh was in the room with the body.
她为什么想杀派克
Why would she want to kill Peck?
他是我们扳倒金的关键证人
He was our key to taking Kim down.
你想证明是别人杀的吗 那就去证明
You want to prove it was someone else? Prove it was someone else.
我知道你觉得这个房地产商是幕后主使
I know you think this real estate guy is behind all this...
房地产只是个伪装
Real estate's his shell, man.
金掌控着市里最大的毒品交易
Kim oversees one of the biggest drug operations in the city.
一半的市领导都会在圣诞节给金寄贺卡
Half the civic leaders in town send Kim Christmas cards.
除了你的观点外
Need more than your opinion
还需要证据来扳倒这样的风云人物
to take on a guy that plugged in.
他说得对 我前几个小时接到了
He's right. I've never gotten calls like I have
有史以来最多的电话
in the past few hours.
-我也是  -谁打来的
- Me, either. - From who?
市里有头有脸的人
People with pull at City Hall.
拜托 这只是金请来
Oh, come on, that's just Kim calling in favors,
打压我的
trying to shut me down.
或者也许他觉得你对他有仇
Or maybe he feels like you got a vendetta,
没有按规矩办事
and haven't exactly been following the rules.
如果我给法务部的马蒂打个电话
If I give Marty in Legal a call,
他能证明你今天去过他的办公室了吗
is he gonna confirm that you stopped by his office earlier?
有人找借口我心里明白得很
I know when I'm getting the runaround.
你和沃尔什都是
From you and Walsh.
我就把话挑明了 在我们调查清楚前
So let me be clear: you're locked in the building
你都不准离开这栋大楼
till we get to the bottom of this.
我知道你和KC关系有多好
I know how close you are to K.C.,
但她已经卸下警徽了 洪都
but she doesn't have a badge anymore, Hondo.
所以我才得帮她
And that's why I needed to help her.
金一天不坐牢
就会让她和她儿子不得安宁
Kim being free is messing with her and her son--
他是我的干儿子
he's my godson.
你确定你没有违规
You sure no lines got crossed?
希克斯抓不住你的把柄
Nothing Hicks can get you for?
你是在问我犯罪了吗
Are you asking me if I got my hands dirty?
我觉得我非常清白
I think I kept them clean enough.
我以为我们能信任彼此
I thought we had trust.
为什么不告诉我你在做什么
Why didn't you tell me what you were doing?
我们确实能信任彼此
We do have trust.
或许我以为我是在保护你
Maybe I thought I was protecting you.
洛克确定吗
Rocker sure about this?
他说等协助逃逸的司机一醒来
Well, he said our getaway driver's amnesia lifted
发现自己被拷在床上失忆症就马上好了
as soon he woke up handcuffed to the bed.
我们第二个枪手用别名潜逃
And our second shooter's traveling under a different name.
但样貌没变 还是大块头 山羊胡
But still a big guy with a goatee?
大块头 山羊胡
还有一张去维加斯的车票
Big guy, goatee and a bus ticket to Vegas.
是那个吗
That our guy?
手背到身后
Give me your hands!
-手背到身后  -婊子
- Give me your hands. - Puta.
闭嘴
Shut up.
拷上了
Got him?
你觉得这里面有多少钱
How much do you think is in there?
-肯定有一万五  -两万
- Got to be 15 large. - 20.
这什么 现在谋杀警察的价格吗
What's that, the going rate for killing cops?
给 孩子
Here you go, kid.
你的脸怎么了
What happened to your face?
我只是出了个小车祸 没事
I just got in a little fender bender. It's nothing.
为什么警察来接我
Why'd the police come and pick me up?
我妈在里面干什么
What's my mom doing back there?
因为你祖母在科罗拉多
Well, since your grandmother's in Colorado,
所以在她回答一些问题的时候
your mom asked me to send a couple guys to pick you up
她叫我派几个人过去接你
while she answers a few questions.
我为什么不能见她
Why can't I see her?
只要她协助完我们查案 你就能见她了
As soon as she's done helping us with our case, you can.
-她不是退休了吗  -是的
- I thought she was retired. - She is.
但这起案子对你妈妈来说真的很重要
But this particular case is really important to your mom,
我们需要她的帮忙
and we need her help.
不如你别再和我玩
"20个问题"的游戏了
Hey, how about you quit with the 20 Questions,
给我点面子 开始看语法书吧
you make me look good and start your grammar.
你知道如果你妈妈觉得我让你偷懒
You know your mom's-a wring my neck
她会扭断我的脖子的
if she thinks I'm letting you slack.
吃东西
And eat.
快吃
Eat.
你这个教父做得挺不错的嘛
You're a hell of a godfather.
这孩子很听话
Kid makes it easy.
我们有什么能帮他的吗
Is there anything we can do for him?
在我们想到办法
如何帮KC摆脱这件事之前
Just keep it a regular day until we figure out
就当没事发生就行了
how to get K.C. out of this.
说到这个 跟我来
Speaking of that, come with me.
洪都 我听说了你的事 很高兴你没事
Hondo, I heard what happened. I'm glad you're okay.
谢谢你  警监
I appreciate that, Commissioner.
几个月前 迈克尔接到杰·金的电话
A few months ago, Michael got a call from Jae Kim.
他说有一名特警队警官
He said a SWAT officer showed up
出现在投资者会议上 说了一些过分的话
at an investor meeting and stepped over the line.
金说他觉得被人恐吓
Kim said he felt threatened,
叫我去调查有关情况
asked me to look into the situation.
我和金说
如果他去找KC·沃尔什或她儿子
I told Kim if he came after K.C. Walsh or her son again,
我就会去找他
I was gonna pay him a visit.
仅此而已
Nothing more to the situation.
你确定吗
Are you sure?
因为当我打电话给缉毒组时
'Cause when I checked in with Narcotics,
他们说你也和他们闹得很激烈
they said you got pretty heated with them, too.
是因为他们没有扳倒杰·金
For not taking Jae Kim down.
所以我再见到金的时候 他说
So when I spoke to Kim again, he said...
等一下 再见到 什么时候
Wait a minute. Again? When?
等等 是因为你 金才知道我过去几个月
Hold up, are you the reason Kim knew I was looking into him
一直在调查他吗
所以我今天才遭遇枪击吗
for the past couple of months? The reason I got shot at today?
我不是有意的 如果真的有调查
That's not what I intended. I never would've spoken to Kim
我是绝对不会和金说
if there was an actual investigation,
但是显然那是你和前联邦探员
but apparently this was you and an ex-federal agent
私下在调查
looking into things on your own?
这我可不知道
I didn't know about it.
你怎么会知道 你坐镇监督委员会
Why should you? You sit on an oversight board.
又不用出外勤
You don't work in the field.
那也不代表你可以走进委员会办公室
Doesn't mean you get to walk into a boardroom
-去恐吓人  -我没恐吓他
- and threaten someone. - I didn't threaten him.
我认识当时委员会里的一些人
I know a some people who were there.
在他们看来那就是恐吓
Sounded like threats to them.
我知道你很聪明 不会违反规章制度
I know you're smart enough not to break the rules,
但是别告诉我 你没有触犯纪律
but don't tell me you didn't bend them here.
杰·金是绑架十岁小男孩的幕后黑手
Jae Kim was behind the kidnapping of a ten-year-old boy.
如果你能证明这点 他早就入狱了
If you could prove that, he'd be behind bars.
或许他只是有很多
Or maybe he just has
像你这样的朋友去帮他掩盖罪行
too many friends like you covering his ass.
少来了 警监
Come on, Commissioner.
不要假装你没听说过
Don't even try to play like you haven't heard
金不干不净的谣言
the rumors of Kim being dirty.
我们过去有过一些来往
We've had a few business dealings in the past,
但我们不是朋友
but we're hardly friends.
至于谣言 也就是谣言
As for rumors, they're rumors.
想要改变架构
You try working in construction
却又不想和有点小问题的人打交道
without dealing with someone who's a little questionable.
那你是什么也打造不出来的
You'd never build anything.
我唯一想在这里打造的是 长官
The only thing I'm trying to build here, sir...
你们俩都别说了
Both of you need to stop.
迈克尔 金想杀死洪都
Michael, Kim tried to have Hondo killed.
洪都 迈克尔不是敌人 我们要达成共识
Hondo, Michael's not the enemy. We need to get on the same page.
什么样的共识
Yeah, and what page is that?
你认得他吗
You recognize him?
凭空冒出一袋钱
Bag of cash came from somewhere.
要告诉我们是谁付给你的吗
Want to tell us who paid you?
没干完活还有这么好的收益
Nice profit for an unfinished job.
是谁叫你干掉我的
Who asked you to take me out?
我认得你
I recognize you.
你拔出一把西格绍尔P228制式手枪
You pulled a SIG P228.
想干掉警察时 你就倒大霉了
Life gets real bad when you go at a cop,
但是你很走运 我只想抓到雇佣你的人
but lucky for you, I just want the guy who hired you.
我不认识他 从来也没和他说过话
I don't know him. Never talked to the guy.
这样可不行啊 迪亚戈
Well, that's not good enough, Diego.
看来你要替所有的人坐牢了 我们走
Looks like you're gonna do time for everybody on this. Let's go.
听着 你们想要抓到那个人吗
Look, listen, look. You want the guy?
你抓到了
All right, you got him.
显然你们已经知道名字了 那你告诉我
Now you obviously got a name, so go ahead and tell me
你希望我重复说给谁听 我都照做
and I'll repeat it to whoever you want me to.
在我耳边悄悄告诉我
Whisper a name in my ear.
警察可不是这么办事的
That's not how we do things here.
听说迪亚戈不愿供出金
Hey. Heard Diego wouldn't give Kim up.
是不能
Couldn't.
金做好了多层保护措施 以自保清白
Kim put enough layers between 'em to keep him in the clear.
那为什么这个杀手还有钱收呢
So why'd this hitman still get paid?
因为他把目标转向了伊恩·派克
'Cause he changed his target to Ian Peck.
如果迪亚戈杀了派克
If Diego killed Peck,
就是说KC就能脱身了吧
that means K.C.'s off the hook, right?
他们正在给他做笔录
They're getting him on the record now,
但是没错 应该会释放KC的
but yeah, K.C. should get released.
太好了 我们能聊两句吗
Great. Hey, could we talk for a sec?
说吧
Shoot.
我妈出狱后就一直住在我家
So my mom's staying with me since she got out,
一切都很好 但既然我是警察
and everything's great, but since I'm a cop,
就要填表格 也就是走走形式
there's this form. It's kind of a formality.
我只是需要上级的同意
I just need approval.
和重罪犯住在一起 可不是走走形式
To live with a felon. It's not a formality.
想得美
Nice try.
那你不会帮我签字吗
So you're not gonna sign for me?
就像安妮和孩子们说的
Look, like Annie tells the kids,
不要兜兜转转走冤枉路
don't take three rights to make a left.
这需要你的上级来签
Your superior officer needs to sign it.
直接去找洪都吧
That's Hondo.
你听说过钱德勒俱乐部吗
Have you heard of the Chandler Club?
市中心那家只对会员开放的酒吧
Yeah, that's that members-only lounge downtown.
洛杉矶那些土得掉渣的富二代
Old money L.A. dinosaurs.
暴发户也可以加入 金是那里的会员
New money, too. Kim's a member.
他刚刚在俱乐部订了一个房间
He just booked a room at the club
向阿尔瓦拉多的投资者
to pitch some high-end development
推销一些高端开发项目
on Alvarado to investors.
那笔2500百万的贷款明天就到期
Oh, okay, so that $25 million loan's due tomorrow,
他出去找摇钱树 想要找点现金
and he's out shaking the tree trying to find some cash.
他急需钱 也许我们可以趁机抓到他
He's desperate. Maybe we can turn that into a bust.
怎么做
How?
迈克尔·普兰克有邀请函
Michael Plank got an invitation.
普兰克 不不 绝对不行 我不相信他
Plank-- No, no. Hell no. I don't trust him.
我相信
Well, I do.
似乎金每几年都会把同样的六处房产
Looks like Kim rotates the same six properties
在其多个公司间流转
among his LLCs every few years.
在法庭上还是没法证明这点
I still can't prove it in court,
但他在为贩毒集团洗钱
but he is laundering money for a cartel.
房产只是用来隐藏毒品利润的方式
The real estate's just a way of hiding the drug profits.
不然这些资金注入就解释不通了
These cash injections make no sense otherwise.
他的公司靠的是沙土[根基不稳]
Company's built on sand.
靠的是芬太尼
It's built on fentanyl.
感谢你给我机会证明我能帮忙
Appreciate you giving me the chance to show you I can help here.
你可以谢谢科尔特斯
You can thank Cortez.
警监  你想帮忙吗
Commissioner, you want to help?
但是这有可能会很危险
Could come with some real danger, though.
上次他追杀那孩子 今天来追杀我
He went after a kid last time and me today.
当我在军械库被人劫持的时候
When I got taken hostage in this armory,
你的直觉帮忙救了我一命
your gut instinct helped save my life.
如果你对金的直觉是对的
If your gut's right about Kim,
我就可以帮忙抓到他 那就是我想做的
and I can help take him down, then that's what I want to do.
你们需要我做些什么
What do you need me to do?
不需要给他设套
Without entrapping him,
我要你让金承认这个开发项目
I need you to get Kim to admit that this development
只是一个洗黑钱的骗局
is just a sham for washing dirty money.
我是一名警监
I'm a police commissioner.
你们为什么觉得他会向我承认
Why do you think he'd admit that to me?
他也许不会
He might not,
但在他追杀我之前 他相信你
but he trusted you before when it came to me.
你是那个房间里对他来说最有用的人
You're gonna be one of the richest men in the room.
金急需2500万美金
Kim needs $25 million quick.
测试一下麦克风
Test the microphone.
一二
One-two.
我都感觉不到麦克风的存在
Wow. I can't even feel it's there.
别这样扭动你的领带 很不自然
Don't touch your tie like that, it's unnatural.
一表现不自然就会暴露你的身份
Unnatural is how covers get blown.
只要让他感觉自在 金很有可能会说一些
Kim's gonna be more likely to say something incriminating
能证明他有罪的话
if he's comfortable.
让他主动来找你
Let him come to you.
普兰克警监
Commissioner Plank.
很高兴你来了
Glad you came.
跨年在纳帕谷没见到你
Missed you in Napa over New Year's.
我在杰克逊霍尔
Jackson Hole for me.
过年不下雪总感觉不对
The holidays just seem wrong without snow.
-失陪了  -请便
‭- Excuse me. - Yeah.
我们队就在附近 如果他说漏嘴
Our team will be nearby, ready to go
或者事情有变 我们随时出动
if he slips or if things go sideways.
-事情有变  -有可能
- Sideways? ‭- It can happen.
所以我的队伍就在屋外的后巷里
So my team's gonna be right outside in the back alley.
我们派了克里斯卧底保护你
We'll send Chris undercover for your protection.
要是他发现我带窃听器了呢
What if he figures out I'm wearing a wire?
不会的 他会相信你
He won't. He's gonna want to believe you.
你只要不想着你带了 就不会露馅
Just forget you're wearing one and you won't screw up.
失陪了
Excuse me.
他要开始了
He's about to start.
试试能不能凑近点
See if you can get closer.
各位请听我说
Excuse me, folks.
谢谢你们这么快赶来
Thank you for coming on short notice.
我可以保证
阿尔瓦拉多的房地产开发项目
I can assure you the property development
绝对值得各位花时间好好了解
on Alvarado is well worth your time.
-你们中有一些人也许还没听说...
-来一杯吗  先生
- For those of you who haven't heard... - ‭Wine, sir?
我在中国的投资人
...my investor in China ran into
因为政府管控遇到了流动性问题
liquidity problems after a government crackdown.
其结果是
The result is
我必须在明天之前
转让他价值2500万的股份
I have to replace his $25 million share by tomorrow.
我知道这听起来有点风险
I realize it sounds aggressive.
我可以让各位匿名加入
I'll let you in on a secret.
现在这些股份已经价值4000万
This share is a $40 million value.
情况很微妙
I'm in a delicate situation.
我给各位朋友们
提供一个一生难得的机会
I'm offering a once in a lifetime deal to my friends.
那么请吧 尽情开怀畅饮 看一看介绍
So please, have a drink, check the specs.
我会到各处为各位答疑
I'll circle around.
幸会
Hey, good to see you.
迈克尔
Michael.
你认识我们之前提到过的那位警官吗
You know that police officer we discussed?
他今天又不请自来了
Paid me another uninvited visit today.
他对我的错误印象真的很严重
‭He really does have quite the wrong impression of me.
我跟他的指挥官交情不错 我会让她
I'm friendly with his commander. I'll get her
确保他不再来骚扰你
to make sure he leaves you alone.
专注他的本职工作
Focuses on his real job.
谢谢你
Thank you.
我说实话
I got to be honest.
投资阿尔瓦拉多
Buying a stake in Alvarado...
我有点兴趣
I'm intrigued.
你的确应该有兴趣
You should be intrigued.
短时间要拿出这么一笔钱是有点多
It's an awful lot on short notice,
但是谁不想用钱生钱呢
but who wouldn't want to turn 25 into 40?
只是有一件事我想确认下
Just one thing I'm not sure about.
我可以让你匿名投资 没有问题 迈克尔
I'd have no problem letting you invest anonymously, Michael.
不 这不是问题
No, that's not a problem.
我们拿得下他吗
Are we gonna get this guy or what?
他好像以为迈克尔上钩了
He seems to think he has Michael on the hook.
如果你还想再谈谈条款
If better terms are what you want...
条款没问题
The terms are fine.
是你的中国投资人的问题
It's your Chinese investor.
你说的这个故事有些地方讲不通
Something doesn't quite add up with that story.
我不介意冒点风险
I don't mind taking risks,
但是我想知道真实情况
but I just need to know the real deal.
你告诉我 我就给钱
You tell me that, I can get you the money.
也许我们这次还是不要合作了
Maybe we wouldn't be good partners in this.
我要去到处走走了
I really should make the rounds.
失陪了 警监
Excuse me, Commissioner.
他差点上钩了
He had him.
-怎么回事  -他太直接了
- What happened? ‭- He was too direct.
又或者他是故意谈崩的
Or he blew it on purpose.
让平民去做警察的工作
Got a civilian doing a cop's job,
就会是这种结果
that's what happened.
我们没有选择的余地
We didn't have a choice.
你快离开这里吧
We should get you out of here.
-我要再去找他谈谈 -不行 迈克尔
- I got to talk to him again. - No, Michael.
你该走了
It's time to go.
门就在你身后迈克尔
Door's right behind you, Michael.
再给我一次机会
Just give me one more shot.
指挥部要求你离开 警监
HQ wants you out, Commissioner.
你先走 我随后就来
You duck out first. I'll be right behind you.
各位
Excuse me, everyone.
各位请听我说
If I can have your attention?
他在干什么
What is he doing?
我想举杯说几句
Love to offer a toast.
杰
Jae...
你是洛杉矶房地产业最后的巨擘之一
you're one of the last true titans of L.A. real estate.
你在这里赚得盆满钵满
You've made millions in this town.
有人说你带来的回报更是不计其数
Some would say you've given even more back.
他们错了
They'd be wrong.
你知道阿尔瓦拉多的项目
不可能带来收益
You know Alvarado won't turn a profit.
是不会盈利的
It can't.
它的价值不到其评估值的一半
It's worth less than half of its assessment.
你说你上个月
You said this property
不费吹灰之力就购入了这片地产
fell into your lap last month,
可你忘了提你是从谁那里买到的
but you failed to mention who you bought it from.
你自己
Yourself.
真的吗
Really?
你就是个骗子
You're a con man.
我不知道你是不是喝多了
I don't know if you've had too much to drink...
我的过往业绩有目共睹
My track record speaks for itself.
那就看大家相信你还是相信我了
It's your word against mine.
给你投资就是让自己的钱打水漂
Whoever invests with you is throwing away their money.
这策略不错  警监
Nice pivot, Commissioner.
谢了
Thanks.
我知道我搞砸了 所以我想
I knew I blew the sting, so I figured
至少我可以阻止金筹钱
the least I could do was stop Kim
这样他就还不清那笔贷款了
from raising the money to pay that loan back.
金不跟你谈的时候
After Kim stopped talking,
-我以为就这么没戏了 -我也是
- I thought it was over. - Yeah, me, too.
我就是没法看着别人
被他的花言巧语哄骗
I just couldn't let Kim sweet-talk someone else
给他递上一张支票
into handing him a check.
所以我就想警告下大家
So, figured I'd poison the well for everyone there,
切断他的保命财路
cut off any financial escape route.
抓不了他 至少让他不好过
Can't bust him, at least keep him desperate.
你现在跟洪都一样 成了活靶子了
Target's on your back now, too. Same as Hondo.
我这条命 就指望你们这些专家
Counting on the pros to prove he's a criminal
来证明他有罪了
before it comes to that.
金肯定会垂死挣扎到底 巴罗斯
Well, Kim's gonna fight to the end. Burrows.
那个任由帮他们逃跑的司机
The Profetas that let our getaway driver
在床上血流不止的先知帮 他们在哪里
bleed all over their mattress-- where are they now?
为什么又叫我过来
So, why'd you bring me back here?
我说了我不知道他们开枪杀警察
I told you I had no idea they shot a cop.
你们开始偷音响之前
Before you started lifting stereos... ‭
先知帮是那个芬太尼赌窝的
...Profetas were the main distributors
主要贩卖商
for a fentanyl operation.
不过你们的生意几个月前泡汤了 对吧
Only business went south a few months ago. Am I right?
货没了
Supply dried up, man.
杰·金的货
Jae Kim's supply.
对
Right.
我有个奇妙的感觉
I got a funny little feeling
供货的口子又要开了
the spigot's about to open up again,
所以我需要你告诉我时间和地点
so I need you to tell me when and where.
我告诉你 就可以自由地离开这里吗
I do that, and I walk out of here a free man?
像鸟儿一样自由
Free as a bird.
也许需要打几个电话
Might have to make a few phone calls.
那我们就给你找一部电话
Well, let's get you a phone, then.
码头旁边有一个装卸区
There's a shipping yard right next to the port.
有交易要发生
Something's going down right now.
大毒贩名叫格拉索
Big dealer named Grasso.
阿明·格拉索 亚美尼亚人
Armin Grasso. Little Armenia.
就是他 他想做芬太尼买卖
That's the one. I guess he's been trying
已经有一段时间了
to tap into the fentanyl market for a while.
今晚他有机会了
Just got his chance tonight.
金要出手了 他要把过去几个月
Kim's making his move. He's unloading
存着的他用来赚快钱的
his entire supply he's been sitting on
库存全部清掉
the past few months for fast cash.
量会很大
That's got to be huge.
价值2500万的芬太尼吗
Like, $25 million worth of fentanyl?
可能还不止 而且金
Probably more. And there's no way
一定会亲自到场监督交易
Kim won't be there personally to oversee this exchange.
出发
Let's move.
你不能跟我们去
You can't come with us.
为什么不能
Like hell I can't.
希克斯不准你出门
Hicks has you grounded.
我回头再请他原谅
I'll beg for forgiveness later.
我们的目标是抓住金
而不是连带你停职甚至更糟
The goal is to bust Kim, not bust Kim and get you suspended. Or worse.
拿下金的时候我必须在场
I'm gonna be there when we take Kim down.
他追杀我的朋友
He went after my friend.
他也追杀了我们的朋友 就是你
He went after our friend, too. You.
听着 我们可以的
Look, we got this covered.
不要冒险毁了诉讼
Let's not risk prosecution.
没事的 洪都
Come on, Hondo.
我们能抓到他
We got him.
我们会扳倒金的
We're gonna take Kim down.
绝不手软
All the way.
换我们中的任何一个人
你也会挺身而出的
You'd do the same thing for any one of us.
去吧  去吧
Go. Go.
听到了吗
Hear that?
那两辆车有动静吗
Anything from the two vehicles?
-没有  -金呢 他出现了吗
- Not a peep. - What about Kim? He show his face?
-还没有  -他很狡猾
- Not yet. - He's slippery.
如果他不出现
If he doesn't show up to this,
我们就没法抓他
we got nothing on him.
继续盯着 右边车里
Keep looking. Three guys
有三个人
in the truck on the right,
左边车里有两个人
two in the car on the left.
都盯紧了
We got 'em both covered.
谭 和指挥部之间的联络怎么样
Tan, how we doing on that line to HQ?
应该马上就好
Should be up in a minute.
有动静
We got movement.
有人看到杰·金了吗
Anyone see Jae Kim?
没有
Nope.
看到他了
Got him.
去把车门打开
Go ahead. Open it up.
记住 在金达成交易之前
Remember, we don't have anything
我们没有关于他的任何把柄
on Kim until he makes a deal.
他一点头 我们就上
The second he gives a nod, we pounce.
这地方很可能会爆炸 准备好
This place might explode, so be ready.
-我们准备好了 老大  -我知道
- We're all over it, boss. - I know you are.
来了
Okay, here we go.
怎么回事 他们要取消吗
What is this? They're calling it off?
卢卡 听到什么了吗
Luca, you hear anything?
没有 声音太小了 而且我高中
No, whispers are too low, and they didn't
也不学亚美尼亚语
teach Armenian at my high school.
这些家伙要么是要进行交易
These guys are either about to make a deal,
要么这地方要炸了
or this place is about to go off.
那里至少有2500万 好了
That's $25 million at least. Here we go.
除非确认交易 否则我们不能上
We can't move in unless there's a confirmation.
握手就行了
A handshake will do.
说定了吗
So, do we have a deal?
说定了
Yeah, we got a deal.
上
Go! Now!
上  上
Move in! Move in!
抓到了  上
We got him! Go!
洛杉矶警局
LAPD! ‭
不许动 洛杉矶警局
Freeze! LAPD!
-举起手来  -去车边
- Hands up! - ‭Get to the car!
-警察  -上
- Police! - Get on him!
洛杉矶警局
LAPD! ‭
放下武器
Drop your weapons now!
趴下
On the ground!
我去抓金
I got Kim!
下车  立刻
Out of the car! Now!
我抓到他了 洪都
I got him, Hondo.
我抓到他了
I got him.
把他抓回来
Bring his ass in.
你好啊 坦纳
Hey. What's up, Tanner?
等等  怎么了
Wait, what's going on?
杰克逊街633号
633 Jackson Street.
嗯  我知道
Yeah, I know it.
好的 伙计 我马上到
All right, man. I'll be right there.
感觉很不错吧
Feels nice, doesn't it?
不仅仅只是不错
Better than nice.
他这种级别的大犯
可不是每天都能遇上的
Don't send his kind away too often.
这种人也不会被关太久
When we do, they don't usually stay there.
我感觉他会被关挺久
I have a feeling this one will stick.
-伙计  -邻居看到有人擅闯
- Hey, man. - Neighbor saw a trespasser.
我到了以后看到有人从窗户里爬出来
When I got here, I saw a figure climbing out the window.
发现她躲在草丛里
Found her hiding in the bushes.
谢谢你先联系我
Thanks for calling me first, man.
我们是应该把抓到的人
We're really supposed to take anyone we find
带回警局
around here into the station.
这片你也很熟 对大家都不好
You know this area. No one's up to any good.
不会再发生这种事了
It's not gonna happen again.
我们不该再这样让你走后门了
We're really not supposed to cut corners anymore.
-别让我因为这个引火烧身 -不会的
- Don't let me get burned for this, man. ‭- You won't.
不会的  我保证
You won't. I promise.
好吧
All right.
谢了
Thanks.
你为什么要回来这里 妈妈
Why'd you come back here, Mom?
我得拿点东西
I had to get something.
我见过这个
I've seen this before.
这是我妈妈除了她的坏脾气以外
Only thing I ever got from my mother,
唯一留给我的东西
except the temper.
你爸爸和我吵得厉害时
When things got bad with your dad and me,
我只是...
我只是觉得有个退路会很好
I just... I thought it would be smart to have an exit strategy.
所以我就把这个藏在了地板下
然后...
So I hid it under the floorboards. And...
之前我都没法回来 直到今天 所以...
Just... I couldn't get back here until today, so...
我要当掉这个 这样
I-I'm gonna pawn it, so that, you know,
在我找到工作之前
你就不用一直负担我的花销
you don't have to cover all my expenses until I get a job.
这里面有很多回忆
A lot of memories in there.
你想进去看看吗
You want to go inside?
不
No.
我从来没想让你这么快长大 吉米
I never, ever meant for you to have to grow up so fast, Jimmy.
真的  我是说
I didn't. I mean,
你爸爸的确不是好人 但
your father was no good, but...
有时候我也不好
neither was I, sometimes.
对不起 对不起
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
没关系
It's okay.
现在都好多了
Things are better now.
我的问题都答对了
I answered every question right,
但是他们还是不要我去上班
but they didn't want me for that job.
我不知道我该怎么办了
I don't know how I'm gonna make it out here.
冠军
Hey, champ.
-你还好吗  -嗯
- How you doing? You good? - Yeah.
听着
Hey, listen.
我要告诉你一些事
I want to tell you something,
你要保证你会永远记得我说的话
and you got to promise you'll always remember.
我保证
Promise.
好
Okay.
你这辈子会听到一个词
There's a word that you're gonna hear
很多很多遍
that gets thrown around a lot in life.
"英雄"
"Hero."
这个词已经流传了好几年
Now, it's been watered down over the years.
这是用来描述那些说了好听话的人
It's something we say when somebody gives a good speech
或者屁股中弹的人
or when somebody gets shot in the butt.
但是当一个人不计回报地
‭But, listen, when a person sticks with something for months
专注于一件事好几个月
and doesn't care if they never get any credit for it
或者就算不是自己的错
or isn't afraid to take the heat
也愿意背负责任
even though it's not their fault,
那才是真正的英雄
that's a real hero.
你妈妈就是那样的人
And that's exactly what your mom is.
-你明白吗  -嗯
- You understand? - ‭Yeah.
很好  去告诉她吧
Good. Go let her know.
车在前门等了
Ride's waiting out front.
酒店都安排好了
The hotel's all set up.
两张床 含欧陆式早餐 公寓式的
Double beds, continental breakfast, the works.
在一切都处理完之前 我们会派
We'll have two officers posted at your door
两名警官随同保护你们
until things settle down.
你们不用这么做的
You don't have to do this.
不是我 是洪都安排的
I didn't. Hondo did.
-你没事吧  -嗯
- You good? - Yeah.
我没事  我只是...
Yeah, I'm fine. I'm just, uh...
我松了一口气
I'm relieved.
你们做得很好
You guys did great out there.
你能帮我个忙吗
Can I ask you a favor?
你竟然没找迪肯
Surprised you didn't ask Deac.
你找了他没同意 对吧
Oh, he didn't go for it, did he?
他说过右转三次不代表左转
Said not to take three rights to make a left.
不管他是什么意思
Whatever that means.
你能签吗
So can you sign it?
你确定这对你来说是最好的选择吗
Are you sure this is what's best for you?
我确定对她来说是最好的选择
I'm sure it's what's best for her.
谢谢
Thanks.
他们来了
There they are.
伙计们  我想...
Real quick, everyone. Um...
简短说几句话
I want to say something.
我曾经有一段时间
There's been times in my life
觉得没有人会做我的后盾
when I didn't feel like people really had my back.
但是今晚你们每个人为我所做的事...
But what each one of you did for me out there tonight...
我真的不知道该说什么
Look, I-I really don't know what to say
只能说我会永远铭记
except I'll never forget it.
谢谢你们
Thank you.